Curiculum Vitae



Dr Siti Hairiah Bt Haji Sariman

Medical Officer UD54

Hospital Jempol

Negeri Sembilan.

0193728757, dr_siti@moh.gov.my

Alternative email: bfcare123@yahoo.com

PROFILE

I am a senior Medical Officer graduated from University Putra Malaysia (UPM) in year 2006 and have been in the service for nearly 13 years. Recently, received master degree on Healthcare Management (Master in Business Administration, Universiti Teknologi Malaysia). Personally, I am good in working in team, goal oriented person, friendly and punctual.

EMPLOYMENT EXPERIENCE

1. House Officer, Hospital Melaka

- Obstetric and Gynaecology Department Posting
- Medicine Department Posting
- Surgery Department Posting

Dates of employment

17th August 2006

17th December 2006

17th April 2007

2. Medical Officer, Hospital Melaka

• Paediatric Department

Orthopaedic Department

• Emergency And Trauma Department

Dates of employment

17th August 2007

17th December 2007

17th April 2008

to 30th November 2008

3.Medical Officer, Klinik Kesihatan Bahau, PKD Jempol, Negeri Sembilan

• Managing Outpatient and Mother Child Health Clinic

Dates of employment

1st December 2008 to

14th June 2014

4.District Health Officer II, PKD Jempol Jabatan Kesihatan Negeri , Negeri Sembilan

5. Medical Officer, PKD Jempol Jabatan Kesihatan Negeri , Negeri Sembilan

Dates of employment

15th June 2014 to 2nd July 2017

Dates of employment

3rd July 2017 till 28th May 2019

6. Medical Officer, Hospital Jempol

Administrative Unit

Dates of employment

29th May 2019 till now

ACADEMIC QUALIFICATIONS

- Master Degree in Bussiness Administration (Healthcare Management) 2019
 Universiti Teknologi Malaysia
 Skudai, Johor
- Degree of Medicine 2006
 Universiti Putra Malaysia
 Serdang, Selangor, Malaysia.

AWARDS

Excellence Service Award; Negeri Sembilan State Health Department; 2014

PROFESSIONAL MEMBERSHIPS

member of Persatuan Kebajikan Perempuan Islam, Negeri Sembilan, Malaysia member of Alumni MBA Healthcare member of Islamic Medical Association of Malaysia

TRAINING AND ATTACHMENT

 Kursus Tatacara Perolehan dan Isu-isu Berkaitan Sebut Harga dan Tender Kerajaan, organized by Institut Pengurusan dan Integriti Melaka

 Good Clinical Practice Course, organized by Clinical Research Center, Ministry of Health Malaysia

3) Bengkel Kuantitatif: Penulisan Proposal dan Perbincangan Dalam Kumpulan, jointly organized by Fakulti Perubatan dan Sains Kesihatan, Universiti Putra Malaysia and Jabatan Kesihatan Negeri Sembilan

$$2^{nd} - 3^{rd}$$
 May 2019

 Bengkel Kualitatif: Teknik Temubual, jointly organized by Fakulti Perubatan dan Sains Kesihatan, Universiti Putra Malaysia and Jabatan Kesihatan Negeri Sembilan

5) Bengkel Kualitatif: Pengenalan Penyelidikan Kualitatif, jointly organized by Fakulti Perubatan dan Sains Kesihatan, Universiti Putra Malaysia and Jabatan Kesihatan Negeri Sembilan

6) Bengkel Ekonomi Kesihatan dan Pengurusan Kewangan Kesihatan, jointly organized by Fakulti Perubatan dan Sains Kesihatan, Universiti Putra Malaysia and Jabatan Kesihatan Negeri Sembilan

7) Bengkel Kuantitatif: Kaedah Penyelidikan, jointly organized by Fakulti Perubatan dan Sains Kesihatan, Universiti Putra Malaysia and Jabatan Kesihatan Negeri Sembilan

8) Global Outreach Program 2019, jointly organized by Azman Hashim International Business School, Universiti Teknologi Malaysia and Jabatan Kesihatan Negeri Sembilan collaboration with Universitas Gadjah Mada, Indonesia

9) Internal Audit Course MS ISO 9001: 2015

```
11<sup>th</sup> -12<sup>th</sup> September 2017
```

10) Bengkel Pembentangan Audit Teknikal Kesihatan Primer, Peringkat Jabatan Kesihatan Negeri Sembilan 2016

```
6<sup>th</sup> – 8<sup>th</sup> September 2016
```

11)Bengkel Transformasi Pembangunan Program Kesihatan Awam Tahun 2014/2015, Jabatan Kesihatan Negeri, Negeri Sembilan

```
16th -18th November 2015
```

12) Kursus Pengurusan Kontrak dan Pengenalan Kepada Outcome Based Budgeting

13) Healthcare Excellence Conference

14) Quality Management Representative MS ISO 9001 : 2008

```
6<sup>th</sup> November 2014
```

15) 17th Malaysian Family Medicine Scientific Conference 2013

16) Management Skill Course Zon Selatan

17) Kursus Kenegaraan PTK Sistem Saraan Malaysia

```
13th-23th March 2009
```

18) Induction Course For Government Officer

PROGRAMMES COORDINATOR

- 1) Credentialing and Privileging of Antenatal Ultrasound for Medical Officer (2014-2019)
- 2) Quality Assurance Programmes Pejabat Kesihatan Daerah Jempol
- 3) Inovative and Creative Group Pejabat Kesihatan Daerah Jempol
- 2) Quality Management System MS ISO 9001: 2008 PKD Jempol (2014-2019)
- 3) Health Promoting Clinic Programme 2015

FACILITATOR

- 1) Majlis Sambutan Minggu Penyusuan Susu Ibu Daerah Jempol 2017 25th August 2017
- Konvensyen Panel Penasihat Klinik Kesihatan Peringkat Negeri Sembilan 2017
 21st February 2017
- 3) Kursus Inspirasi Diri (Motivational Course) 10th 11th Oktober 2016
- 4) Kursus Medicolegal Untuk Anggota Kesihatan : Etika dan Perundangan 1st July 2015
- 5) Kursus Orientasi Anggota Kesihatan Daerah Jempol (Tahun 2017-2019)
- 6) Bengkel Pemantapan Penyelia (Tahun 2019)
- 7) Bengkel Penilaian Risiko Sistem Pengurusan Kualiti MS ISO 9001:2015 Pejabat Kesihatan Daerah Jempol (Tahun 2017-2018)
- 8) Kursus Audit Dalam Sistem Pengurusan Kualiti MS ISO 9001:2015 Pejabat Kesihatan Daerah Jempol (Tahun 2016-2018)

REFEREES

1) Dr Zul Iskandar Bt Zainudin

Pengarah Hospital

Hospital Jempol

Negeri Sembilan

0192624043

dr_zul@moh.gov.my

2) Dato' Dr Zainuddin Bin Mohd Ali

Pakar Perubatan Kesihatan Awam

Pengarah Kesihatan Negeri

Jabatan Kesihatan Negeri Sembilan

0132189811

drzainudin@gmail.com